[
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(1)?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "2",
      "1",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(2)?",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "3",
      "4",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(3)?",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "4",
      "9",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(4)?",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "5",
      "16",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(5)?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "6",
      "25",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(6)?",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "7",
      "36",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(7)?",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "8",
      "49",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(8)?",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "9",
      "64",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(9)?",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "10",
      "81",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(10)?",
    "options": [
      "20",
      "11",
      "100",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(11)?",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "12",
      "121",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "22"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(12)?",
    "options": [
      "24",
      "13",
      "144",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(13)?",
    "options": [
      "26",
      "14",
      "169",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "26"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(14)?",
    "options": [
      "28",
      "15",
      "196",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "28"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(15)?",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "16",
      "225",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "30"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(16)?",
    "options": [
      "32",
      "17",
      "256",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "32"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(17)?",
    "options": [
      "34",
      "18",
      "289",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "34"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(18)?",
    "options": [
      "36",
      "19",
      "324",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(19)?",
    "options": [
      "38",
      "20",
      "361",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "38"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(20)?",
    "options": [
      "40",
      "21",
      "400",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "40"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(21)?",
    "options": [
      "42",
      "22",
      "441",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "42"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(22)?",
    "options": [
      "44",
      "23",
      "484",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "44"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(23)?",
    "options": [
      "46",
      "24",
      "529",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "46"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(24)?",
    "options": [
      "48",
      "25",
      "576",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "48"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(25)?",
    "options": [
      "50",
      "26",
      "625",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "50"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(26)?",
    "options": [
      "52",
      "27",
      "676",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "52"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(27)?",
    "options": [
      "54",
      "28",
      "729",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "54"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(28)?",
    "options": [
      "56",
      "29",
      "784",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "56"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(29)?",
    "options": [
      "58",
      "30",
      "841",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "58"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(30)?",
    "options": [
      "60",
      "31",
      "900",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "60"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(31)?",
    "options": [
      "62",
      "32",
      "961",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "62"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(32)?",
    "options": [
      "64",
      "33",
      "1024",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "64"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(33)?",
    "options": [
      "66",
      "34",
      "1089",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "66"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(34)?",
    "options": [
      "68",
      "35",
      "1156",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "68"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(35)?",
    "options": [
      "70",
      "36",
      "1225",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "70"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(36)?",
    "options": [
      "72",
      "37",
      "1296",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "72"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(37)?",
    "options": [
      "74",
      "38",
      "1369",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "74"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(38)?",
    "options": [
      "76",
      "39",
      "1444",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "76"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(39)?",
    "options": [
      "78",
      "40",
      "1521",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "78"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(40)?",
    "options": [
      "80",
      "41",
      "1600",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "80"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(41)?",
    "options": [
      "82",
      "42",
      "1681",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "82"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(42)?",
    "options": [
      "84",
      "43",
      "1764",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "84"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(43)?",
    "options": [
      "86",
      "44",
      "1849",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "86"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(44)?",
    "options": [
      "88",
      "45",
      "1936",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "88"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(45)?",
    "options": [
      "90",
      "46",
      "2025",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "90"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(46)?",
    "options": [
      "92",
      "47",
      "2116",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "92"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(47)?",
    "options": [
      "94",
      "48",
      "2209",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "94"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(48)?",
    "options": [
      "96",
      "49",
      "2304",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "96"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(49)?",
    "options": [
      "98",
      "50",
      "2401",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "98"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(50)?",
    "options": [
      "100",
      "51",
      "2500",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "100"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(51)?",
    "options": [
      "102",
      "52",
      "2601",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "102"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(52)?",
    "options": [
      "104",
      "53",
      "2704",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "104"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(53)?",
    "options": [
      "106",
      "54",
      "2809",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "106"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(54)?",
    "options": [
      "108",
      "55",
      "2916",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "108"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(55)?",
    "options": [
      "110",
      "56",
      "3025",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "110"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(56)?",
    "options": [
      "112",
      "57",
      "3136",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "112"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(57)?",
    "options": [
      "114",
      "58",
      "3249",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "114"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(58)?",
    "options": [
      "116",
      "59",
      "3364",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "116"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(59)?",
    "options": [
      "118",
      "60",
      "3481",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "118"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(60)?",
    "options": [
      "120",
      "61",
      "3600",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "120"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(61)?",
    "options": [
      "122",
      "62",
      "3721",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "122"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(62)?",
    "options": [
      "124",
      "63",
      "3844",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "124"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(63)?",
    "options": [
      "126",
      "64",
      "3969",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "126"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(64)?",
    "options": [
      "128",
      "65",
      "4096",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "128"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(65)?",
    "options": [
      "130",
      "66",
      "4225",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "130"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(66)?",
    "options": [
      "132",
      "67",
      "4356",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "132"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(67)?",
    "options": [
      "134",
      "68",
      "4489",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "134"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(68)?",
    "options": [
      "136",
      "69",
      "4624",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "136"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(69)?",
    "options": [
      "138",
      "70",
      "4761",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "138"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(70)?",
    "options": [
      "140",
      "71",
      "4900",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "140"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(71)?",
    "options": [
      "142",
      "72",
      "5041",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "142"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(72)?",
    "options": [
      "144",
      "73",
      "5184",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "144"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(73)?",
    "options": [
      "146",
      "74",
      "5329",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "146"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(74)?",
    "options": [
      "148",
      "75",
      "5476",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "148"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(75)?",
    "options": [
      "150",
      "76",
      "5625",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "150"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(76)?",
    "options": [
      "152",
      "77",
      "5776",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "152"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(77)?",
    "options": [
      "154",
      "78",
      "5929",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "154"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(78)?",
    "options": [
      "156",
      "79",
      "6084",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "156"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(79)?",
    "options": [
      "158",
      "80",
      "6241",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "158"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(80)?",
    "options": [
      "160",
      "81",
      "6400",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "160"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(81)?",
    "options": [
      "162",
      "82",
      "6561",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "162"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(82)?",
    "options": [
      "164",
      "83",
      "6724",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "164"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(83)?",
    "options": [
      "166",
      "84",
      "6889",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "166"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(84)?",
    "options": [
      "168",
      "85",
      "7056",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "168"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(85)?",
    "options": [
      "170",
      "86",
      "7225",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "170"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(86)?",
    "options": [
      "172",
      "87",
      "7396",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "172"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(87)?",
    "options": [
      "174",
      "88",
      "7569",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "174"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(88)?",
    "options": [
      "176",
      "89",
      "7744",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "176"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(89)?",
    "options": [
      "178",
      "90",
      "7921",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "178"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(90)?",
    "options": [
      "180",
      "91",
      "8100",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "180"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(91)?",
    "options": [
      "182",
      "92",
      "8281",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "182"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(92)?",
    "options": [
      "184",
      "93",
      "8464",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "184"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(93)?",
    "options": [
      "186",
      "94",
      "8649",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "186"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(94)?",
    "options": [
      "188",
      "95",
      "8836",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "188"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(95)?",
    "options": [
      "190",
      "96",
      "9025",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "190"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(96)?",
    "options": [
      "192",
      "97",
      "9216",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "192"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(97)?",
    "options": [
      "194",
      "98",
      "9409",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "194"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(98)?",
    "options": [
      "196",
      "99",
      "9604",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "196"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(99)?",
    "options": [
      "198",
      "100",
      "9801",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "198"
  },
  {
    "type": "mcq",
    "question": "[DSA] What is the result of function call dsa_func(100)?",
    "options": [
      "200",
      "101",
      "10000",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "200"
  }
]